Ahmed Mohmed Osman

Software engineer

Respectful self-motivator gifted at finding reliable solutions for software issues. Experienced in Flutter and Dart and offering skills in React and Web development and Front-end development overall. Fluent in English and accustomed to working with cross-cultural, global teams.

ahmedxosman98@gmail.com

Dubai, UAE

in linkedin.com/in/ahmed-osman-61783223a

+971503471099

www.behance.net/ahmedxosman

github.com/ahmedos999

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology Sudan University Of Science & Technology

11/2016 - 03/2022

Khartoum/Sudan 3.35 GPA

SKILLS



WORK EXPERIENCE

Application EngineerRaiba Land Transport /El Nefeidi Group

06/2022 - Present Khartoum/Sudan ERP Microsoft dynamics 365 business central for Transports business Achievements/Tasks

- ERP implementation for big company with 10 departments.
- System support & Training for 3 major Departments.
- Requirements analysis for 3 modules.

Teaching AssistantSudan University Of Science & Technology

06/2022 - 09/2022

Khartoum/Sudan

Achievements/Tasks

- Data Structures and algorithms with java for more than 100 students.
- Microsoft office Programs for 1st Grade.
- CMD commands and windows for 1st Grade.

Freelance Developer self-employed

03/2022 - Present

using learned skills for freelancing projects

Achievements/Tasks

- Flutter Framework using Bloc pattern to build mobile 3 projects built.
- Web development in freelance sites using React.js with 2 react projects.
- Front-end Development transform UI/UX design in code over 10 design into code.

PROJECTS

pharmacies Management system and medicines finding system (Graduation Project) (06/2021 - 03/2022)

- a platform that helps the pharmacies to manage their pharmacy business process and customers finding their medicines and ordering
- The project mobile application communicating with web application through APIs, Using provider as state management project done through team work with 4 other developers
- Project link:https://www.behance.net/gallery/158530103/Pharma-mobile-application

E-Store Web application (React)

- Web application for E-commerce project using react and Html/CSS.
- website contains full shopping system from the landing page to the payment receipt with 5 Pages.
- Project link: https://www.behance.net/gallery/179360695/E-store-Web-Application.

E - Commerce Mobile Application (Flutter)

- E store mobile application designed with adobe XD implemented with flutter framework with 2 language support.
- involves simple yet beautiful interfaces with shopping cart functionally with 8 Screen.
- login/register system, billing system, the project involves dealing the JSON file for the data, and River pod for state management.
- Project link:https://www.behance.net/gallery/158602249/E-store-Mobile-Ap.

LANGUAGES

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Arabic Er

English

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Book reading Gym Technology Travelling